howtogettheguy.com 2018-07-06

# Privacy Policy | Get The Guy

We are committed to maintaining the trust and confidence of all our clients, readers, viewers and website visitors by ensuring that your privacy is protected.

Our business is based on adding value to the lives of our users through our emails, newsletters, blogs, videos, online programmes and all other media.

Most importantly we do not sell, rent or trade our information, email lists, or any other visitor data with any other companies for marketing purposes, we never have and never will.

We keep the minimum information necessary to enable us to add as much value as possible for you.

This Privacy Policy provides the detail on the information we collect and why, how we use it, and how we keep it secure. Should we ever ask you to provide any information by which you can be identified when using this website, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement.

## What information do we collect?

We may collect the following information depending on which of our services or programmes you choose to access:

  * Contact information including email addresses

  * Name, age and job title

  * Demographic information such as address, postcode or IP address

  * Other information relevant to customer surveys and/or offers

## What do we use the information for?

We only collect the minimum information appropriate to deliver to you the service you are accessing and we only ever use this information to better understand your needs and provide you with a better service.

So, we use this information for the following:

  * To deliver our products and services
  * To improve our products and services

  * To periodically send promotional emails about products, special offers or other information which we think you may find interesting and beneficial using the email address you have provided

  * Internal record keeping

## Security

We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorised access or disclosure we have put in place suitable electronic, physical and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.

When you purchase a programme we normally only collect your name, email and contact number, but for some programmes this may include additional information such as address and job title. This information may be stored in our system, or with third party cloud-based services such as Infusionsoft and Maropost who may be used for the provision of our online services to you. These third party services are responsible with us for processing and safeguarding your data and as such comply with this Privacy Policy.

## Transaction Security

We believe in the strictest guidelines when payments are taken. When placing your order with us online all information regarding your method of payment (whether by credit card or debit card) is passed through a secure checkout operated by a third-party payment gateway (Vindicia and Paypal). This ensures your card details are handled in the most secure, efficient and confidential manner. These third-party payment gateways are controlled by their own strict guidelines which keep your information secure and private and we choose them because they are the world’s leading experts in performing these transactions.

## Phishing

We will never send you an email asking you for any personal information, this includes your address details or payment details. If you receive an email which appears to be from us asking for this information then please contact us immediately straight and do not reply to such an email.

## Links to other websites

Our website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement.

You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.

## Access to, or Deletion of, your Personal Information

You are entitled to view, amend, or delete any of your information that we hold.  
Simply email your request to our data protection officer using any of the contact forms on our website or mail your request directly to data@howtogettheguy.com

If you believe that any information we are holding on you is incorrect or incomplete, please email us as soon as possible. We will promptly correct any information found to be incorrect.

You can unsubscribe from our emails at any time you choose with one click using the unsubscribe link included in the footer of every email we send you which will also remove you from our weekly free video coaching blog mailing.

## Updates

This policy will be continually updated in line with improving best practice, developing technology and changes to legislation. You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you are happy with any such changes.

This policy is effective from 1st May 2018.
